A Guide to the Virginia Intercollegiate Association Papers 1954-1969
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Administrative Correspondence
  - Subject Schools Correspondence
    - Officials Martinville Board 1956-1967 (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Board of Officials Martinsville 1968-1969 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Northern Neck 1954-1956 (Box-folder 27:10)
    - Officials-Northern Board 1957-1958 (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Officials Northern Neck 1959-1964 (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Petersburg Board 1955,1967 (Box-folder 27:13)
    - Board of Officials Petersburg 1968-1969 (Box-folder 27:14)
    - Constitution Petersburg Board 1956 (Box-folder 27:15)
    - Piedmont Board 1961-1965 (Box-folder 27:16)
    - Roanoke Board 1961 (Box-folder 27:17)
    - Salem Board 1954-1958 (Box-folder 27:18)
    - Salem Board 1955-1956 (Box-folder 27:19)
    - Salem Board 1959-1962 (Box-folder 27:20)
    - Salem Board 1963-1966 (Box-folder 27:21)
    - Southside Board 1955-1958 (Box-folder 27:22)
    - Southside Board 1959-1962 (Box-folder 27:23)
    - Southside Board 1962-1967 (Box-folder 27:24)
    - Board of Officials-Southside 1968 (Box-folder 27:25)
    - Staunton Board 1955-1959 (Box-folder 27:26)
    - Staunton Board 1960-1963 (Box-folder 27:27)
    - Tri-City district Board of Officials 1967 (Box-folder 27:28)
    - Board of Officials Tri-City (Box-folder 27:29)
    - Outline Map of Virginia (Box-folder 27:30)
    - Purchasing Office Correspondence 1965-1968 (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Purchasing Agent (Mr. Brown) (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Purchasing Agent (Mr. Brown) 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Purchasing Directory 1955 (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Proposed change Instructer of Council (Box-folder 28:5)
    - Programs 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - Qualified Football Officials 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - Realignment Committee 1965-1966 (Box-folder 28:8)
    - Recommendations 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Report of Game Results (Box-folder 28:10)
    - Reservations 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28:11)
    - Reservations 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28:12)
    - Reservations 1966-1968 (Box-folder 28:13)
    - Requisitions (Correspondence) 1955-1960 (Box-folder 28:14)
    - Requisitions 1961-1965 (Box-folder 28:15)
    - Requisitions Forms 1954-1955 (Box-folder 28:16)
    - Requisitions Inter-Development 1959-1968 (Box-folder 28:17)
    - Room Accomodations 1965-1960 (Box-folder 28:18)
    - Science Math Conference Budget & Expenses 1967-1968 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1954-1955 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1956-1957 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1957-1958 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1958-1959 (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1959-1960 (Box-folder 29:8)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1960-1961 (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1962-1963 (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box-folder 29:12)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box-folder 29:14)
    - Science and Math Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 29:15)
    - Printed Math and Science 1955-1956 (Box-folder 29:16)
    - Printed Science and Math (Box-folder 29:17)
    - Science Math Constitution 1955-1956 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - Science Math (Rules) (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Science Math (Planning Committee) Minutes 1957 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - Science Math Conference Reports 1965-1966 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Science Math Activities 1956-1957 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - Science Math Conference Activities 1957-1958 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - Science Math Conference Activities 1958-1959 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - Science Math Conference Scholarships 1965-1966 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - Science Math Conference 1956,1962 (Box-folder 30:9)
    - Science Math Conference 1967-1968 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - Science Math Test 1955-1956 (Box-folder 30:11)
    - Science Math Conference Participating Schools 1961-1962 (Box-folder 30:12)
    - Science Math Conference Participating Schools 1962-1963 (Box-folder 30:13)
    - Science Math Test 1956-1957 (Box-folder 30:14)
    - Science Math Test 1959-1960 (Box-folder 30:15)
    - Science Math Conference Test 1962-1963 (Box-folder 30:16)
    - Science Math Conference (Quizzes) 1957-1958 (Box-folder 30:17)
    - Science Math Quizzes 1960-1961 (Box-folder 30:18)
    - Science Math Quizzes 1961-1962 (Box-folder 30:19)
    - Sanction Meets 1967-1968 (Box-folder 31:1)
    - School Enrollment 1953 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - Social Science Research 1958-1959 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - Scholastic Sports Carnival 1956-1958 (Box-folder 31:4)
    - Correspondence- Other Scholastic Organization 1964-1965 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Sportsman Rules 1967 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - Sportsman Rules 1968 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - Sportsman Rules Proposed (Box-folder 31:8)
    - Souvenir Program Letters (Box-folder 31:9)
    - Souvenir Program 1968-1969 (Box-folder 31:10)
    - Special Meets 1967-1968 (Box-folder 31:11)
    - Student Participation Association. Conference Programs 1958-1965 (Box-folder 31:12)
    - Student participation Association. Workshop Reports 1959 (Box-folder 31:13)
    - Student participation Association. Awards (Box-folder 31:14)
    - Student participation Association. Newsletters 1961,1967 (Box-folder 31:15)
    - Student Participation Association Newsletters 1955-1958 (Box-folder 31:16)
    - Student Participation Association Newsletters 1959-1960 (Box-folder 31:17)
    - Souvenir Program Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 31:18)
    - Student Participation Association Formation 195-1956 (Box-folder 31:19)
    - Student Participation Association Minutes 1955 (Box-folder 31:20)
    - Student Participation Association Financial 1955 (Box-folder 31:21)
    - Student Participation Association Conference Proceedings 1956 (Box-folder 31:22)
    - Student Participation Association Workshop Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 31:23)
    - Student Participation Association Workshop Corespondence 1959 (Box-folder 31:24)
    - Student Participation Association Conference Reports Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31:25)
    - Student Participation Association Reports 1956 (Box-folder 31:26)
    - Student Participation Association Workshop Report 1958 (Box-folder 31:27)
    - Student Participation Association Report 1959 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - Student Participation Association Correspondence 1954-1955 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Student Participation Association Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 32:3)
    - Student Participation Association Correspondence 1956-1958 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - Student Participation Association Correspondence 1958-1962 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - Student Participation Association Correspondence 1963, 1966 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - Student Participation Association Correspondence 1967, 1968 (Box-folder 32:7)
    - Student Participation Association Newsletter Correspondence 1957-1959 (Box-folder 32:8)
    - Sportsmanship Rules 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32:9)
    - Sportmanship Rules 1968 (Box-folder 32:10)
    - Sportsmanship Rules (Box-folder 32:11)
    - Subscriptions (Books,Magazine,Newspapers) (Box-folder 32:12)
    - Tennis Correspondence 1954-1959 (Box-folder 32:13)
    - Tennis Tournament Correspondence V.I.A. & A.T.A. 1955-1959 (Box-folder 32:14)
    - Tennis Correspondnece V.I.A. & A.T.A. 1960-1966 (Box-folder 32:15)
    - Tennis Tournament Results (Box-folder 32:16)
    - Tennis Tournament (Participating Schools) 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32:17)
    - Tennis Tournament 1967 (Box-folder 32:18)
    - Tennis Tournament 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32:19)
    - Tennis Tournament 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32:20)
    - Track Meet V.I.A.L. 1954 (Box-folder 32A:1)
    - Correspondence Track 1954-1955 (Box-folder 32A:2)
    - Tournament Statistics 1954-1955 (Box-folder 32A:3)
    - Track 1955-1956 (Box-folder 32A:4)
    - Track & Field 1962-1963 (Box-folder 32A:5)
    - Track 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32A:6)
    - Track 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32A:7)
    - Track Meet 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32A:8)
    - Track Meet 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32A:9)
    - Track & Field 1956-1957 (Box-folder 32A:10)
    - Track & Field 1958-1959 (Box-folder 32A:11)
    - Track & Field Meet 1959-1960 (Box-folder 32A:12)
    - Track & Field Meet 1958-1959 (Box-folder 32A:13)
    - Track & Field 1960-1961 (Box-folder 32A:14)
    - Track & Field 1963-1964 (Box-folder 32A:15)
    - Track Meet 1964-1965 (Box-folder 32A:16)
    - Track & Field Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32A:17)
    - Track 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32A:18)
    - Track Meet 1967 (Box-folder 32A:19)
    - Track Meets 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32A:20)
    - Track Distrct Records 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32A:21)
    - Track Eligibility Forms 1969 (Box-folder 32A:22)
    - Track Entries and District Records (Box-folder 32A:23)
    - Track Entries 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32A:24)
    - Treasurer- Comptroller 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32A:25)
    - Transfers 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32A:26)
    - Transfers Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32A:27)
    - Transfer Rules 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32A:28)
    - Treasurer Comptroller (Mr. Cedhas) 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32A:29)
    - Treasurer Comptroller (Box-folder 32A:30)
    - Unassigned 1957-1961 (Box-folder 32B:1)
    - University Center in Virginia Memo 1957 (Box-folder 32B:2)
    - University of Virginia 1954-1956 (Box-folder 32B:3)
    - The Vaughan Company (Box-folder 32B:4)
    - Virginia State Bulletins 1960-1961 (Box-folder 32B:5)
    - V.I.A. Track Records (Box-folder 32B:6)
    - V.S.U. Counseling Service (Box-folder 32B:7)
    - V.S.U. Federal Credit Union (Box-folder 32B:8)
    - Virginia Education Association (Box-folder 32B:9)
    - Virginia Teacher Association 1954-1968 (Box-folder 32B:10)
    - Virginia High School League 1954-1955 (Box-folder 32B:11)
    - Virginia High School League 1955-1956 (Box-folder 32B:12)
    - Virginia High School League 1956-1958 (Box-folder 32B:13)
    - Virginia High School League 1959-1960 (Box-folder 32B:14)
    - Virginia High School League 1961-1963 (Box-folder 32B:15)
    - Virginia High School League 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32B:16)
    - Virginia High School League 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32B:17)
    - Virginia Secondary School Principal (Box-folder 32B:18)
    - Virginia Education Association 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32B:19)
    - V.I.A. Announcements 1957 (Box-folder 32B:20)
    - V.I.A. Member School High School Enrollment (Box-folder 32B:21)
    - V.I.A.- V.H.S. L. Joint Proposal (Box-folder 32B:22)
    - Vice President M. Walker H. Quarles, Jr. 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32B:23)
    - Virginia High School League 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32B:24)
    - Virginia High School League 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32C:1)
    - V.I.A. 1968 (Box-folder 32C:2)
    - V.I.A. Calendar of Activities 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32C:3)
    - V.I.A. Passes Issued 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32C:4)
    - V.T.A. 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32C:5)
    - V.T.A. (Box-folder 32C:6)
    - V.T.A. (Box-folder 32C:7)
    - V.T.A. Department of Secondary Schools Principals 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32C:8)
    - Washington Met 1954-1955 (Box-folder 32C:9)
    - Wrestling 1955-1956 (Box-folder 32C:10)
    - Wrestling 1963-1965 (Box-folder 32C:11)
    - Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 32C:12)
    - Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 32C:13)
    - Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 32C:14)
    - Correspondence November-December 1955 (Box-folder 32C:15)
    - Correspondence January - February (Box-folder 32C:16)
    - Correspondence March-April 1956 (Box-folder 32C:17)
    - Correspondence May-June 1956 (Box-folder 32C:18)
    - Correspondence July 1956 (Box-folder 32C:19)
    - Correspondence September - December 1956 (Box-folder 32C:20)
    - Correspondence January - February 1957 (Box-folder 32C:21)
    - Correspondence March - April 1957 (Box-folder 32C:22)
    - Correspondence May-June 1957 (Box-folder 32C:23)
    - Correspondence July-August 1957 (Box-folder 32C:24)
    - Correspondence September - October 1957 (Box-folder 32C:25)
    - Correspondence November-December 1957 (Box-folder 32C:26)
    - Correspondence January-Febrauary 1958 (Box-folder 32C:27)
    - Correspondence March-April 1958 (Box-folder 32C:28)
    - Correspondence May, June-August (Box-folder 32C:29)
    - Abrams, S.C. High School 1955-1969 (Box-folder 33:1)
    - Addison, Lucy C. High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - Addison, Lucy High School 1960-1968 (Box-folder 33:3)
    - Armstrong High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - Armstrong High School 1958-1966 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - Augusta co. Junior High School 1954-1966 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - Bethune, Mary High School 1956-1959 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Bethune, Mary High School 1964-1966 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - Bethune, Mary High School 1966-1967 (Box-folder 33:9)
    - Bethune, Mary High School 1967-1969 (Box-folder 33:10)
    - Blackwell High School 1961-1966 (Box-folder 33:11)
    - Brookvale High School 1959-1969 (Box-folder 33:12)
    - Burton Heights High School 1954-1968 (Box-folder 33:13)
    - Bunche, Ralph High School 1954-1968 (Box-folder 33:14)
    - Burley, Jackson P. High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 33:15)
    - Burley, Jackson P. High School 1959-1964 (Box-folder 33:16)
    - Burley, Jackson High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 33:17)
    - Campbell County High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 34:1)
    - Campbell High School 1959-1963 (Box-folder 34:2)
    - campbell County High School 1963-1968 (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Carver, George Washington High School- Chesapeake 1954-1958 (Box-folder 34:4)
    - Carver, George Washington High School- Newport News 1954-1960 (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Carver-Newport News 1961-1967 (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Carver-Chesapeake 1962-1963 (Box-folder 34:7)
    - Carver George Washington- Chester 1954-1969 (Box-folder 34:8)
    - carver George Washington- Fieldale 1954-1959 (Box-folder 34:9)
    - Carver George Washington- Fieldale 1960-1962 (Box-folder 34:10)
    - Carver George Washington- Fieldale 1965-1966 (Box-folder 34:11)
    - Carver George Washington- Rapidan 1954-1967 (Box-folder 34:12)
    - Carver George Washington- Salem 1954-1959 (Box-folder 34:13)
    - Carver High School-Salem 1960-1966 (Box-folder 34:14)
    - Central High School-Charlotte 1954-1964 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - Central High School-Armherst 1956-1959 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - Central High School-Charlotte 1965-1968 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - Central Academy-Fincastle 1956-1965 (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Central High School-Goochland 1958-1965 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Central Academy-Fincastle 1966-1969 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Central High School-Healthsville 1957-1967 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Central High School-Irwin 1954-1958 (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Central High School-King and Queen 1954-1966 (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Central High School-Sussex 1959-1967 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - Central High School-Patrick(Stuart) 1954 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - Christiansburg High School 1954-1956 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - Christianburg High School 1956-1960 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - Christianburg High School 1963-1965 (Box-folder 35:14)
    - Christianburg High School 1960-1963 (Box-folder 35:15)
    - Clarke, S.H. Junior School 1958-1967 (Box-folder 35:16)
    - Crestwood High School 1954-1962 (Box-folder 35:17)
    - Crestwood High School 1963-1968 (Box-folder 35:18)
    - Crestwood Junior High School 1963-1968 (Box-folder 35:19)
    - Criser High School 1959-1966 (Box-folder 35:20)
    - Dean, Jennie High School 1959-1964 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Douglas High School- Bristol 1954-1967 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Douglas Junior High School 1965-1967 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Douglas High School-Leesburg 1954-1966 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Douglas High School-Winchester 1954-1959 (Box-folder 36:5)
    - Douglas High School-Winchester 1960-1966 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Downing Lylburn High School 1954-1957 (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Downing, Lylburn High School (Lexington) 1958-1965 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Dunbar High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - Dunbar High School (Lynchburg) 1960-1962 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Dunbar High School (Lynchburg) 1963-1969 (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Emma, St. Military Academy 1954-1965 (Box-folder 36:12)
    - Emma, St. Military academy 1966-1967 (Box-folder 36:13)
    - End, East High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 36:14)
    - End, east High School (South Hill) 1960-1963 (Box-folder 36:15)
    - End, East High School 1964-1969 (Box-folder 36:16)
    - West End High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 36:17)
    - End, West High School 1961-1966 (Box-folder 36:18)
    - Essex County High School 1954-1965 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - Essex County High School 1966-1969 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - Foster Luther H. High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Foster, Luther H. High School 1960-1964 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Foster Luther H. High School 1965-1969 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Franklin County High School 1954-1956 (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Gandy, John M. High School 1954-1962 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Gandy, John M. High School 1963-1969 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - Gibson, Susie High School 1954-1963 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Gibson, Susie G. High School 1964-1968 (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Grant Walker High School 1954-1961 (Box-folder 37:11)
    - Grant Walker High School 1962-1968 (Box-folder 37:12)
    - Gray, Parker High School 1954-1956 (Box-folder 37:13)
    - Gray, Parker High School 1957-1960 (Box-folder 37:14)
    - Gray, Parker High School 1961-1963 (Box-folder 37:15)
    - Gray, Parker High School 1964-1965 (Box-folder 37:16)
    - Grares, Benjamin Jr. High School 1962-1963 (Box-folder 37:17)
    - Grove, Russell High school 1954-1968 (Box-folder 37:18)
    - Halifax County High School 1954-1955 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Harris, Albert High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Harris, Albert High School 1961-1969 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - Hayden, High School 1954-1963 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Hayden, High School 1965-1968 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Hoffman, Boston High School 1960-1966 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - Hoffman, Boston High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - Holmes, Hamilton High School 1954-1969 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - Hunter, Thomas High School 1954-1968 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - Huntington High School 1958-1962 (Box-folder 38:10)
    - Huntington High School 1963-1968 (Box-folder 38:11)
    - Huntington High School 1954-1957 (Box-folder 38:12)
    - Jackson, Luther High School (Cumberland) 1954-1958 (Box-folder 38:13)
    - Jackson, Luther P. High School (Cumberland0 1960-1968 (Box-folder 38:14)
    - Jackson, Luther P. High School (Dendron) 1954-1969 (Box-folder 38:15)
    - Jackson, Luther P. High School (Merrifield) 1954-1964 (Box-folder 38:16)
    - Jacox, D.G. Jr. High School 1954-1966 (Box-folder 38:17)
    - Jefferson High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 38:18)
    - Jeffferson High School 1961-1965 (Box-folder 38:19)
    - Johnson, A.T. High School 1954-1969 (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Johnson, James Weldon, High School 1954-1966 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Kennedy, John F. High School 1964-1968 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Langston, John M. High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Langston, John M. High School 1959-1968 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Lee, Arty High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Lunenburg High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Lunenburg High School 1961-1968 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Luray, West High School 1962-1965 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - manassas, Regional High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Moton, Robert R. High School 1954 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Moore, J.E.J. High School 1954 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - Nansemond, Co. High School 1954-1962 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Nelson Memorial High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - Nelson Memorial High School 1960-1968 (Box-folder 39:15)
    - Norcom I. C. High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 39:16)
    - Norcom, I.C. High School 1961-1968 (Box-folder 39:17)
    - Northampton County High School 1954-1961 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Northampton County High School 1962-1968 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Northside High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - Northside High School 1961-1969 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Peabody High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 40:5)
    - Peabody High School 1961 (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Phoenix, George P. High School (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Phoenix, George P. High School 1961-1968 (Box-folder 40:8)
    - Pocahontus High School 1954-1968 (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Pode, H.H. High School 1958-1963 (Box-folder 40:10)
    - Price-Carver High School 1954-1960 (Box-folder 40:11)
    - Price, Carver High School 1961-1969 (Box-folder 40:12)
    - Princess Anne County High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 40:13)
    - Randolph Jr. High School (Richmond) 1962 (Box-folder 40:14)
    - Randolph, Virginia High School 1954-1959 (Box-folder 40:15)
    - Randolph, Virginia High School 1960-1969 (Box-folder 40:16)
    - Richardson, A.G. High School 1954-1963 (Box-folder 41:1)
    - Richardson, A.G. High School 1964-1969 (Box-folder 41:2)
    - Richmond County High School 1954-1969 (Box-folder 41:3)
    - Riverview High School 1963-1967 (Box-folder 41:4)
    - Rosenwald, Julius High School- Beverlyville 1954-1958 (Box-folder 41:5)
    - Rosenwald High School-Healthsville 1957-1958 (Box-folder 41:6)
    - Rosenwald, Jr. High School-Waynesboro 1954-1964 (Box-folder 41:7)
    - Ruffner, Jr. High School 1964-1966 (Box-folder 41:8)
    - Russell, J.S. High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 41:9)
    - Russell, J.S. High School 1959-1968 (Box-folder 41:10)
    - Ruthville High School 1954-1969 (Box-folder 41:11)
    - Scott Memorial High School 1954-1965 (Box-folder 41:12)
    - Simms, Lucy High School 1954-1965 (Box-folder 41:13)
    - Smith, Mary Rottingham High School 1954-1966 (Box-folder 41:14)
    - Southampton County High School 1951-1960 (Box-folder 41:15)
    - Southampton County High School 1961-1963 (Box-folder 41:16)
    - Southside High School-Blairs 1954 (Box-folder 41:17)
    - Southside High School-Blairs 1961-1968 (Box-folder 41:18)
    - Southsode High School-Dinwiddie 1954-1956 (Box-folder 41:19)
    - Southside High School-Norton 1954-1957, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 41:20)
    - Southwestern High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 41:21)
    - Suffolk, East High School 1954-1956 (Box-folder 41:22)
    - Sussex County High School 1954-1956 (Box-folder 41:23)
    - Taylor, Lewin W. High School 1954 (Box-folder 42:1)
    - Taylor Williams County High School 1954-1956 (Box-folder 42:2)
    - Taylor, W.C. High School 1964-1968 (Box-folder 42:3)
    - Tazewell County High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 42:4)
    - Thomas, Y.H. Jr. High School 1962-1963, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42:5)
    - Tyler, George High School 1957-1959 (Box-folder 42:6)
    - Tyler, George High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 42:7)
    - Union High School (Bowling Green) 1960-1963 (Box-folder 42:8)
    - Union High School 1963-1964 (Box-folder 42:9)
    - Union High School 1967-1968 (Box-folder 42:10)
    - Union- Kempsville High School 1961-1963 (Box-folder 42:11)
    - Union- Kempsville High School 1967-1968 (Box-folder 42:12)
    - Victory, Our Lady High School 1954-1957 (Box-folder 42:13)
    - Waid, Lee High School 1956-1963 (Box-folder 42:14)
    - Waid, Lee M. High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 42:15)
    - Walker, Maggie L. High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 42:16)
    - Walker, Maggie L. High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 42:17)
    - Walker, Maggie L. High School 1962-1967 (Box-folder 42:18)
    - Walker, St. Clare High School 1954 (Box-folder 42:19)
    - Walker, St. Clare High School 1964-1963 (Box-folder 42:20)
    - Walker, T.C. High School 1954-1967 (Box-folder 42:21)